It's not that I want to live happily ever after...
Nor am I looking to be promised something definite.
But more than that...
Some place beyond, there should be...
- ...the place where I want to be.
You don't have to go all the way to a university in Tokyo...
We don't have cram schools here to help you prep...
Gotta go to cram school, later man.
Isn't he testing for uni this year?
I wonder when he studies...?
- Interesting.
-Is something the matter?
No, it's just that these two are so alike...
Same simple mistakes, same thinking behind their proofs.
(Well done!)
Subtitle by zkaipr
Resync by amin20thapril
Don't get too down on yourself even if you don't get in.
...Well here I go!
Heading out, bye.
Oh, it's today, isn't it? I wonder how it went for those kids...
I'm not alone anymore.
Director: Makoto Shinkai
Animation: Masayoshi Tanaka
Song: "Crossroad" sung by Yanaginagi
Voices
Miho: Ayane Sakura
Shota: Kensho Ono
Instructor: Masahiko Tanaka