Machiko!
Honey!
Where are we?
I dont know.
I dont remember a thing.
You too?
You mean you dont either?
Please, come in.
Welcome to Quindecim.
Allow me to formally introduce myself. I am Decim, your bartender.
Hello.
Now, then. If you will indulge me,
I must ask you a question.
Do you remember anything that happened just before your arrival?
No, nothing.
Although...
I think we were on our honeymoon.
Youre right! I remember that much, at least.
Very good.
Thank you very much.
So tell us... What is this place?
Allow me to explain your circumstances.
I ask that you pay close attention.
First:
I cannot tell you where you are.
Second:
The two of you are here to play a game.
A game?
Third:
The game you play will be chosen via roulette.
Fourth:
Your lives will be staked on this game.
W-Wait a minute!
Fifth:
Until the game is over,
you cannot leave this bar.
What?
Lets go, Machiko. This guys not worth our time.
O-Okay.
Poor bastards off his rocker.
Huh?
Just a bathroom.
Damn it.
How do we get out of here?
You cannot leave the bar until the game is over.
And if we refuse to play your game?
I would not recommend that.
Wh-Whats going on?
Honey, are those...
What the hell?
Are those actually bodies?
This is all I can tell you:
You are here to play a game on which your lives depend.
Whats this guy up to?
If you would go ahead and press this button, the roulette will commence...
and the game will be chosen.
Honey...
Lets just go along with it for now.
Theres no telling what he might do if we dispute him.
Good thinking.
The rules are simple.
You will take turns throwing each of the darts in front of you until one of you reaches a score of zero.
In the event that you run out of darts before that happens,
the one with the lowest score will be declared the winner.
You each have seven darts.
Please be mindful of the throw line at your feet.
The outer ring nets you double points,
and the inner ring nets you triple.
A single-bull is worth 25 points,
and a double-bull is worth 50.
There are regions of the body inscribed on the targets,
each of which is linked to a set of your nerves.
What was that?
Theyre "linked" to us?
Yes. If pierced by a dart, you will feel pain.
Well what?!
The higher the score, the greater the pain will be.
Y-You cant be serious.
I...
Calm down.
You know that cant be true.
Lets just keep playing along for now.
But...
If worst comes to worst,
Ill find us a way out of this.
Honey...
Well, then.
Let us begin the game.
"Linked", my ass.
Even the idea is ridiculous.
Machiko!
Youre kidding me!
It couldve been my imagination.
It was just a little twinge.
It doesnt hurt anymore.
Thank you. Im fine.
But...
Calm down, dear.
Let me give it a try.
Honey!
Did it actually hurt you?!
That settles it.
How the hell are they doing this?
Did something stab me?!
No, theres nothing.
Honey!
Just wait there!
You cant fool me that easy!
Im a doctor!
There arent any signs of surgery.
What did you do to us?!
Nothing in particular.
Then what is this pain?!
I was very clear.
In this game, your lives are on the line.
If you wish to avoid the pain, you do not have to hit the target.
What?
If you miss with the rest of your darts, the game will come to an end.
Oh, yeah.
We could always do that instead.
In that case, Machiko would be declared the winner.
Id lose?
Whats going on, honey?
Takashi?
Oh...
It sounds like we have to keep playing the game.
But he just gave me quite the tip.
All we have to do is miss.
Itll be over before we know it.
We can do that?
Yeah.
But if we do, then youll lose.
Dont let that get to you.
Its fine.
It doesnt matter who wins or loses.
I still have Machiko.
Whats the matter?
Its your turn.
Oh, right.
Sorry.
Shit!
Im sorry, Machiko!
My hand slipped!
I-Its all right, honey.
Thanks.
My eyes!
Im sorry, dear!
Are you okay?
You just had to hit the double!
I didnt do it on purpose! Honest!
Im sorry, honey. Im so sorry!
Forgive me.
Please dont!
Please, at least...
not in the stomach.
Not at your child.
What? Are you serious?
Yes.
Now that I think about it,
you have been out of sorts lately.
Yeah.
How many weeks?
Ten.
Why didnt you say anything?
I wanted to surprise you on our honeymoon.
I still havent told anyone.
I wanted you to be the first to know.
Really?
Thank you, Machiko.
Try not to overexert yourself.
Okay.
Im sorry.
So Im finally going to be a father.
How could you...
I didnt do it on purpose.
Liar! What if something happened to the baby?!
Wh-What?
I cant believe I let something so important get away from me.
What are you talking about?
Dont give me that.
That was such a lovely ceremony.
Yeah. Macchi sure does play to win, doesnt she?
Youre telling me.
Macchi? Do they mean Machiko?
Come to think of it,
shes always been a smooth operator, hasnt she?
I hear her husbands another doctor.
And shes got a stud on the side. Im so freaking jealous!
I heard every word they said.
Your friends really have no class.
Whats that supposed to mean?
Imagine finding out on your wedding day that your wife is having an affair.
I dont know what youre talking about!
Still, I couldnt bring myself to stop the ceremony.
I just kept trying to block out what theyd said.
Im telling you, youve got it all wrong!
I was so in love with you!
And I love you, too! You dont know what youre saying!
Dont lie to me!
Im not lying! Its the truth!
You and I are through.
Tell me something.
What is it?
Theres more to the game than those rules, isnt there?
That ones not yours.
That may be,
but the rules didnt say anything about who can throw each dart.
Am I wrong?
You are correct.
As long as a dart hits a target, points are scored.
They planned on us taking from each other from the start.
Seven darts were never enough.
You are down to one final dart,
so the next person to score will be the winner.
What happens to the loser?
I am terribly sorry, but I cannot answer that.
You heard the man.
I think its about time I showed Ms. Play-to-Win the taste of defeat. How about it, Macchi?
Ill bet youve never lost, eh?
"Macchi"?
Thats your nickname, isnt it?
Do you remember me telling you about my friend at our wedding who I hadnt seen in years?
Machida Yuuki.
Shed always hated her name back in high school.
She said it sounded too masculine.
What are you saying?
So we nicknamed her "Macchi".
What?
She married a doctor several years ago,
but fretted about being unable to break it off with an old boyfriend.
Youre lying!
You think Im making this up, too?
Macchi sure does play to win, doesnt she?
I hear her husbands another doctor.
I-It cant be.
Then you mean...
the baby is...
I havent lied to you at all.
Machiko! Wait a minute!
Wait, I...
Enough already!
Ill show you!
Dont!
No...
Congratulations.
Machiko is the winner.
The game is hereby at an end.
Both of you, please proceed this way.
Hold on!
Not yet! Just give me one more try!
Youre too late!
What was that?!
Its too late...
for any of this.
Machiko...
Tell me.
We...
Were dead, arent we?
Yes.
The two of you have already passed on.
Following their deaths,
people are sent to either Heaven or Hell.
Quindecim exists to preside over that judgment.
There is a provision that states that those pairs who die at the same moment may be invited here.
I apologize for being unable to tell you earlier.
Why dont you answer it?
Huh?
I just dont feel like talking.
Give me that! Ill answer it!
Hey, cut it out!
The road! Watch the road!
Were dead?
How could this have happened?
I just...
wanted to start a happy family.
I wanted to be our protector.
How could I have killed my own child?
Thats ludicrous!
Please help us!
Youre God, arent you?!
I am merely an arbiter.
Please! This cant seriously be happening!
Shut up! You can drop the fucking act already!
"Act"?
That is not my child!
Then whose do you think it is?
Another mans, of course!
Takashi...
Youre right.
The thing is...
I love someone else.
I mean, Id have to, right?
Did you honestly think someone was going to fall in love with you?
What are you, brain-damaged?!
I was obviously after your money!
You...
So this whole time, its been nothing but lies!
Of course I was lying! Who the hell would want to have your child?!
You dirty bitch!
Fuck!
What is this?!
The game is already over.
I dont give a shit!
Let me go!
I am terribly sorry. The ruling has already been passed down.
Let me hit her!
Let me go, damn it!
Forgive me.
Lets be off.
This way.
Well, then.
I bid you farewell.
Nice job!
Thank you very much.
What did you think?
It was awful.
Youll get used to it soon.
Where did each of them end up going?
Takashis soul was sent for reincarnation,
and Machikos was sent into the void, right?
Yes.
I see.
Um...